Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local Union 190 records 1950-1980 IBT0044
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Local Union 190 Records
1950-1980
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0044
0.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains the records of International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local Union 190. The records of agreements, correspondence, meeting minutes, and strikes and pickets range in date from 1950 to 1980. The parts of the collections donated by Rohrer are clearly marked.
Arrangement
Organized into 4 series: Agreements, Correxpondence, Meeting Minutes, and Strikes and Pickets
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the records of International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local Union 190. The records of agreements, correspondence, meeting minutes, and strikes and pickets range in date from 1950 to 1980. The parts of the collections donated by Rohrer are clearly marked.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Labor unions
- Agreements, 1950-1980; Series 1; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Agreements - Rhorer, 1950-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1950-1980; Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Correspondence - Rohrer, 1950s; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Rohrer, 1960s; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Rohrer, 1970s; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Rohrer, 1980s; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Rohrer, Undated; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Meeting Minutes, 1950-1980; Series 3; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Meeting Minutes - Rohrer, 1950s; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Strikes and Pickets, 1970s; Series 4; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Strikes and Pickets - Rohrer, 1970s; Series 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)